{
  "title": "Assessment: Changes in Matter",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "The process of solids turning into liquid.",
      "choices": ["Melting", "Freezing", "Evaporation", "Sublimation"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the reverse of the melting process.",
      "choices": ["Icing", "Freezing", "Evaporation", "Sublimation"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "It occurs when wet clothes dry out in the sun.",
      "choices": ["Melting", "Freezing", "Evaporation", "Sublimation"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of solids turning directly to gas.",
      "choices": ["Melting", "Freezing", "Evaporation", "Sublimation"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What temparature does ice start melting to water?",
      "choices": ["0 Celsius", "32 Celsius", "10 Celsius", "64 Celsius"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a product of freezing?",
      "choices": ["Water", "Juice", "Candy", "Ice Cream"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Steam is formed when water is evaporated.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Solid mothballs will eventually turn into gas.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Water vapor is formed by melting.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Freezing helps preserve food.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
